What we need to do here is, so now we are going to focus on selecting the right rows and columns.
And this is 60% of what you actually do in pandas. So two things here which I would like to explain
first. So let's take a look at this row first, this line. So first use of AND and R. So this is
AND Boolean operator, this one. And there could be a similar, the pipe symbol R in Boolean.
Not Python's AND or R, but those don't work on arrays. Condition in parenthesis. So we can see
here we have put our conditions in parenthesis. Don't worry, I'll explain the rest of the code
down the line. So you can see we have one condition and two conditions in parenthesis.
And this trips up everyone once. Now it won't trip you up. Second is this dot query on the next line.
Is underused for multi-condition filters, like where we are checking region is equal to north
and revenue greater than 5,000. It is dramatically more readable than stacked Boolean expressions.